Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
- Box: 120, Folder: 17 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: WBF In Action Vol. 86, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 17)
    January/February 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: WBF In Action Vol. 86, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 17)
    May/June 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: WBF In Action Vol. 86, No. 4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 17)
    July/August 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: WBF In Action Vol. 86, No. 5, Publication (Box 120, Folder 17)
    September/October 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: WBF In Action Vol. 87, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 17)
    January/February 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: WBF In Action Vol. 87, No. 6, Publication (Box 120, Folder 17)
    November/December 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: WBF In Action Vol. 87, No. 5, Publication (Box 120, Folder 17)
    September/October 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: WBF In Action Vol. 87, No. 4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 17)
    July/August 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: WBF In Action Vol. 87, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 17)
    May/June 1993. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 18 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Solidarity Vol. 78, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    January/February 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Solidarity Vol. 78, No. 4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    July/August 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Solidarity Vol. 79, No. 2, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    March/April 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Solidarity Vol. 79, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    May/June 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Solidarity Vol. 79, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    January/February 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Solidarity Vol. 79, No. 4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    July/August 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Solidarity Vol. 79, No. 5, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    September/October 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Solidarity Vol. 79, No. 6, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    November/December 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Solidarity Vol. 80, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    January/february 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Solidarity Vol. 80, No. 2, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    March/April 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Solidarity Vol. 80, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    May/June 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Solidarity Vol. 80, No. 4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    July/August 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Solidarity Vol. 80, No. 5, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    September/October 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Solidarity Vol. 80, No. 6, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    November/December 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Solidarity Vol. 81, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    January/February 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Solidarity Vol. 81, No. 2, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    March/April 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Solidarity Vol. 81, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    May/June 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Solidarity Vol. 81, No. 5, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    September/October 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Solidarity Vol. 81, No. 6, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    November/December 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Solidarity Vol. 82, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    January/February 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Solidarity Vol. 82, No. 2, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    March/April 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Solidarity Vol. 82, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    May/June 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Solidarity Vol. 82, No. 4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    July/August 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Solidarity Vol. 82, No. 5, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    September/October 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Solidarity Vol. 82, No. 6, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    November/December 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Solidarity Vol. 83, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    January/February 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Solidarity Vol. 83, No. 2, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    March/April 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Solidarity Vol. 83, No. 5, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    September/October 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Solidarity Vol. 83, No. 6, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    November/December 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Solidarity Vol. 84, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    January/February 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Solidarity Vol. 84, No. 2, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    March/April 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Solidarity Vol. 84, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    May/June 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Solidarity Vol. 84, No. 4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    July/August 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Solidarity Vol. 84, No. 5, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    September/October 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Solidarity Vol. 84, No. 6, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    November/December 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Solidarity Vol. 85, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    January/February 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Solidarity Vol. 85, No. 2, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    March/April 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Solidarity Vol. 85, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    May/June 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Solidarity Vol. 85, No. 4, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    July/August 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Solidarity Vol. 85, No. 5, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    September/October 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Solidarity Vol. 85, No. 6, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    November/December 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Solidarity Vol. 83, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 18)
    May/June 1989. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 19 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Ten Years of Work Experience of Philadelphia Weavers and Loom Fixers, Publication (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Production Employment and Productivity in 59 Manufacturing Industries, Part Three: Appendixes, Publication (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Trade-Union Policy and Technological Change, Publication (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Production Employment and Productivity in 59 Manufacturing Industries, Part One: Purpose, Methods, and Summary of Findings, Publication (Box 120, Folder 19)
- Box: 120, Folder: 20 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: "Subversive Activities in New Hampshire", Publication (Box 120, Folder 20)
    January 5, 1955. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 21 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Outline of Talk Given at the World Peace Workshop, Wooster, Ohio, November 13, 1953, Publication (Box 120, Folder 21)
    By K. E. Boulding. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 22 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Worldwatch Paper 25: Worker Participation--Productivity and the Quality of Work Life, Publication (Box 120, Folder 22)
    December 1978. Item is in English.
- Box: 120, Folder: 23 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Worthington News Vol. V, No. 1, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Worthington Headquarters News Letter, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
    October, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: You and Worthington, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Worthington Holyoke Division: News Letter, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Worthington Standard Pump Division News Letter, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
    August 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Management News Letter, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
    By C. A. Butcher. November, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Worthington Corporation Correspondence, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: Worthington Corporation: Organization of Administrative Staff and Operating Divisions, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: World Wide Operations, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: If Henry Worthington only knew what his little companywas up to., Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: This is Worthington, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Item 12: Comprison: Union Contract Provisions as of June 1, 1966, Publication (Box 120, Folder 23)
- Box: 120, Folder: 24 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: A Word About Wykoff and You, Publication (Box 120, Folder 24)
- Box: 120, Folder: 25 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Wyman-Gordon Company Annual Report for the year ended December 31, 1967, Publication (Box 120, Folder 25)
    Released February 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Wyman-Gordon Company Six Months Report for the period ended July 4, 1970, Publication (Box 120, Folder 25)
    Released August 5, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Wyman Gordon Company Six Months Report for the period ended June 28, 1969, Publication (Box 120, Folder 25)
    Released July 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Wyman-Gordon Company Six Months Report for the period ended June 29, 1968, Publication (Box 120, Folder 25)
- Box: 120, Folder: 26 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Progress and Paths of Xerox, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
    By Joseph C. Wilson, Sol M. Linowitz, C. Peter McClough. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Standards for Selecting Salesmen, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Benefits: Xerox, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Employee Matching Gifts Programs, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Affirmative Action Management Guide, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: How Xerography Works, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
    Rochester, New York. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Xerox World/Special Section: The Center in Leesburg, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: A Short History of Xerox, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: Xerox Unit's Mission, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
    February, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Employee Selection, Publication (Box 120, Folder 26)
- Box: 120, Folder: 27 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Looking Ahead into 1947, Publication (Box 120, Folder 27)
    By W. Girson Carey, Jr. January 8, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Incentive Plan Agreed to by Yale & Towne Manufacturing Company and I.A.M., Publication (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: The 100% Allowed Hour Incentive Plan, Publication (Box 120, Folder 27)
- Box: 120, Folder: 28 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Labor and Management Center Publications, Publication (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Labor and Management Center Plans and Progress, Publication (Box 120, Folder 28)
    By E. Wight Bakke. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Guide to Discipline, Publication (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Guide to Grievance Handling, Publication (Box 120, Folder 28)
- Box: 120, Folder: 29 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Yale University Personnel Manual: Administrative Offices, Laboratories, and Library, Publication (Box 120, Folder 29)
- Box: 120, Folder: 30 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The Home Front and Labor's War Record, Publication (Box 120, Folder 30)
    By E. C. Worman. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Savings and Security Plan for Non-Secretarial Employees of the Young Women's Chrisian Association: Seventh Annual Report of the President, Publication (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: The Young Women's Christian Association Retiremnet Fund Incorporated: Twenty-second Annual Report of the President, Publication (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Public Affairs New Service: Building a Responsible Labor Movement Vol. 10, No. 3, Publication (Box 120, Folder 30)
    February 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Program Exchange, Publication (Box 120, Folder 30)
    November 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: How Starched are White Collars Today?, Publication (Box 120, Folder 30)
- Box: 120, Folder: 31 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Representation of Employees, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Representation of Employees, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: The Youngstown Story, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    By J. L. Mauthe. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Strike Nobody Wanted, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: The Truth About Profits, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 6: The Youngstown Sheet & Tube Company Employees' Relief Association: Chicago District, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    Book No. 4; Printed June 1945; Organized March 27, 1924; Amended June 1, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company Employees' Benefit Association: Youngstown District Articles of Membership, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    Approved March 16, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    Reprinted June 1, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Youngston District Operations, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    September 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Indiana Harbor Works, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    May 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company Correspondence, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    February 5, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company Correspondence, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    March 5, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company Correspondence, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    March 16, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company Correspondence, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    June 22, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company Correspondence, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    July 3, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company Correspondence, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    August 5, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Safety First, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 18: Rules and Instructions: Third Edition, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    July 1917. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Welcome The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 20: Industrial Housing, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    By W. W. Boyd, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: "Letter to Youngstown", Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 22: 75 Years, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 23: Visit to Youngstown, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 24: A Visit to the Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Item 25: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company Correspondence, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
    September 14, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: The Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company Correspondence, Publication (Box 120, Folder 31)
- Box: 120, Folder: 32 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Educational Classes and Other Service with Workingmen, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
    By Fred H. Rindge, Jr., M. A. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Developing the Cooperative Spirit through The Man Next to the Men, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
    By Charles R. Townson. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Incentive and Initiative, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
    By Charles P. Steinmetz. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Story of Industry, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
    By Leon Pratt Alford. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: In Camp with the Builders, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: Creative Spirit in Industry, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
    By Robert b. Wolf. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Foremanship, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Item 8: The College Man's Opportunity, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Item 9: Facts about Labor Leaders, Worker Opinions, White Collar Workers, Foremen's Unionc, Public Opinion about Unions, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Item 10: The Story of Labor-Saving Machinery, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
    By George F. Barber. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Twenty Questions on Economic Security of the People: A Study Outline, Publication (Box 120, Folder 32)
- Box: 120, Folder: 33 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Zenith: Profit-Sharing and You, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Safety and the Zenith Employee, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Zenith Radio Corporation: Corporate Employee Relations Policy Manual, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: Zenith Radio Corporation: Corporate Employee Relations Policy Manual, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Supervisor's Labor Relations Manual, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
    March 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Welcome to Zenith, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: Supervisor's Labor Relations Manual, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
    February, 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Employees' Salary Administration Manual, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
    August 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Proposed Induction Program for New Supervisory Personnel, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Item 10: Setting Up a Supervisory Development Program, Publication (Box 120, Folder 33)
    By J. M. Wadsworth. August 31, 1950. Item is in English.
- Text digitized from the collection., Publication (Box 121)